directexpose.com 2019-09-29

# PRIVACY POLICY | DirectExpose

**NOVELTY MAGAZINES LTD. PRIVACY POLICY**

This Novelty Privacy Policy was last updated on May 31, 2019.

We, Novelty Magazines Ltd. and our corporate affiliates (“ **Novelty** “, “ **we** ” or “ **us** “), are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We are the company responsible for the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information under this Privacy Policy. _We believe in transparency and want you to feel comfortable using our platform, and we are committed to being upfront about our privacy practices._

  1. ******Introduction**

  * **Scope of this Privacy Policy  **

This Privacy Policy explains the information we collect from you when you access and use the Novelty family of websites (each, a “ **Site** ” and collectively, the “ **Site** “), as well as our platforms, widgets, analytics tools, and other technical applications that we may provide either through our Sites or through third-party websites or other products and services provided by us (which, together, are referred to as the “ **Services** ”), how we use and disclose such information. We also wish to make sure that you are aware of the options available to you when you access and use our Services.

  * **Contact Us  **

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Novelty Magazines Ltd.

Email address: [contact@novelty.media](mailto:contact@novelty.media)

Postal address: Habarzel 1, Tel Aviv, Israel 6971001

  * **Third-Party Links  **

The Site may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect information about you. We do not control these third-party services and are not responsible for their privacy, information, or other practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website or other online service that you visit or use.

  2. ******Personal Information**

“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual. If you choose to contact us by using the forms provided on our Site, you may choose to provide Personal Information to us, such as your full name, email address, phone number, job title, and company. If you disclose any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the Services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  

  3. ******Use of Personal Information**

We and our service providers use Personal Information for legitimate business purposes, including to:

  * **Provide the functionality of the Services and fulfill your requests.**
    * To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as when you contact us by using the forms provided on our Site.

We will engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you and/or to comply with a legal obligation.

  * **Aggregate and/or anonymize Personal Information.**

  * We may aggregate and/or anonymize Personal Information so that it will no longer be considered Personal Information. We do so to generate other information for our use, which we may use and disclose for any purpose. 

  * Accomplish our business purposes.

  * For data analysis, for example, to improve the efficiency of our Services; 

  * For audits, to verify that our internal processes function as intended and are compliant with legal, regulatory, or contractual requirements; 

  * For fraud and security monitoring purposes, for example, to detect and prevent cyberattacks or attempts to commit identity theft; 

  * For developing new products and services; 

  * For enhancing, improving, or modifying our current products and services; 

  * For identifying usage trends, for example, understanding which parts of our Services are of most interest to users; 

  * For determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, so that we can adapt our campaigns to the needs and interests of our users; and 

  * For operating and expanding our business activities, for example, understanding which parts of our Services are of most interest to our users so we can focus our energies on meeting our users’ interests.

We engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you, to comply with a legal obligation, and/or because we have a legitimate interest.

  4. ******Disclosure of Personal Information**

Your Personal Information will be disclosed:

  * **To our affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy , including to Novelty Magazines Inc., a Delaware corporation, Songo Media Inc., a Delaware corporation, and Songo Media Ltd., an Israeli entity.**

  * To our third-party service providers, to facilitate services they provide to us. These can include providers of services such as website hosting, data analysis, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, auditing, and other services. 

**Other Uses and Disclosures**

We also use and disclose your Personal Information as necessary or appropriate, especially when we have a legal obligation or legitimate interest to do so:

  * **To comply with applicable law and regulations , which can include laws outside your country of residence. **

  * To cooperate with public and government authorities, to respond to a request or to provide information we believe is important. These can include authorities outside your country of residence.

  * To cooperate with law enforcement, such as when we respond to law enforcement requests and orders or provide information we believe is important, including to law enforcement outside your country of residence.

  * For other legal reasons, such as to enforce our terms and conditions and to protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you, or others. 

  * In connection with a sale or business transaction. We have a legitimate interest in disclosing or transferring your Personal Information to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) Such third parties may include, for example, an acquiring entity and its advisors. 

  5. ******Other Information**

“Other Information” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individual. We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use and disclose it for the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information as detailed in this Privacy Policy. In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information. If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined. 

  6. ******Cookies and Tracking**

When you use or interact with our Services, we or our service providers automatically collect certain information, such as your browser and device information, IP address, and information collected through cookies and similar technologies. We use this information to ensure that the Services function properly, for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, to understand and measure how the Services are used, to improve and resolve questions regarding the Services, to resolve When visiting our Site for the first time, you will be prompted to provide consent for our use of cookies questions about them, and to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

To learn more about how we use cookies, or to opt out of the collection and use of cookies, please see our Cookie Notice, which is incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.

We do not currently respond to browser do-not-track signals.

  7. ******Jurisdiction and Cross-Border Transfer**

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and, by using the Services, you understand that your information will be transferred to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country. In certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in those other countries may be entitled to access your Personal Information.

  8. **** **Retention Period**

We retain aggregated or anonymous information, which cannot identify an individual or device and is used for purposes of reporting and analysis, for as long as necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

  9. **** **Information Security**

We have put in place security measures designed to prevent Personal Information from being accidentally lost or acquired, used, accessed, altered, or disclosed in an unauthorized way. Please keep in mind that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of your Personal Information may have been compromised during, or as a result of, your use of the Services), please immediately notify us in accordance with the “Contact Us” section above.

  10. ******Protection of Children’s Privacy**

We are concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the internet. Our Services are not directed to children under eighteen (18). 

We will never knowingly request Personal Information online from anyone under the age of 18 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our Services are general audience sites and are not targeted to or intended for use by children. However, if we learn that we have received information from a child under the age of 18 without parental consent, we will delete that information from our database.

  11. ******Choices and Access**

If you would like to request to review, correct, update, suppress, restrict, or delete Personal Information, object to the processing of Personal Information, or if you would like to request to receive an electronic copy of your Personal Information for purposes of transmitting it to another company (to the extent these rights are provided to you by applicable law), you may contact us at [contact@novelty.media](mailto:contact@novelty.media) or Habarzel 1, Tel Aviv, Israel 6971001. We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law.

For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion. 

  12. ******Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page. Your use of the Services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. 

  13. ******Additional Information Regarding the European Economic Area**

If you are located within the European Economic Area, you may lodge a complaint with a data protection authority for your country or region or where an alleged infringement of applicable data protection law occurs. A list of data protection authorities is available at [http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/GVKtCmZM8ki2Bq0BH312ig).

**NOVELTY MAGAZINES LTD. COOKIE NOTICE**

Last revised: May 31, 2019

This Cookie Notice (“ **Notice** ”) explains more about how Novelty Magazines Ltd. and its affiliates (“ **Novelty** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”) and our authorized service providers, may use cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies (collectively “ **cookies** ”) on our websites (including [www.directexpose.com](http://www.directexpose.com/)) (the “ **Sites** ”), as well as your choices related to such use.

We may change this Notice at any time. Please refer to the top of this page for the date this Notice was last revised. Any changes in this Notice will become effective when we post the revised Notice to this Site.  This Notice is incorporated in and part of our Privacy Policy.

**About cookies**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that a web server transmits to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies. A persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and remain valid until its expiration date, unless it is deleted by the user, while a session cookie will expire when the web browser is closed at the end of the user session.

Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal data that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. Cookies enable a website to remember your actions and preferences over a period of time, so you don’t have to repetitively enter certain information, perform certain action or configure certain aspects of a website whenever you return to the website or browse from one page to another. More information about cookies and how they work is available at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**Cookies that we use**

We use cookies to:

  * Identify you when you visit our Site and as you navigate our Site
  * Analyze the use and performance of our Site and services
  * Display advertisements that will be relevant to you
  * Store your preferences in relation to the use of cookies more generally

  * Maintain your session
  * Remember your language and origin settings 
  * Remember your past searches on our Sites
  * Remember your location
  * Remember your preferences

**Cookies used by our service providers**

Analytics/Performance Cookies: Our service providers use cookies that may be stored on your computer when you visit our Site.

**Google Analytics.**  We use Google Analytics. Google Analytics gathers information about the use of our Site by means of cookies. This information is used to create reports about the use of our Site. You can find out more about Google’s use of information by visiting [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) and you can review Google’s privacy notice at [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). If you want to opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics, visit the Google Analytics Opt-out page at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and install the add-on for your browser.

**Facebook Analytics.**  We use a Facebook pixel on our Site. Using the pixel, Facebook collects information about the users and use of our Site. The information is used to personalize Facebook advertisements and to analyze the use of our Site. To find out more about the Facebook pixel and about Facebook’s use of personal data generally, see the Facebook cookie policy at [https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/) and the Facebook privacy policy at [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy). If you are a registered Facebook user, you can adjust how advertisements are targeted by following the instructions at [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217), and you may opt out from tracking by the Facebook pixel under [https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads).

**Other Third-Party Cookies.** We also use other third party service providers, such as Comscore, Taboola, Quantcast, and Outbrain, which may use cookies for interest-based advertising and behavior analytics. Specifically, you may receive advertisements based on information relating to your access to and use of the Services and other websites or online services on any of your devices, as well as on information received from third parties. These companies place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags). They also use these technologies, along with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop. If you would like more information about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit [http://optout.aboutads.info/#/](http://optout.aboutads.info/), [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](about:blank).

**Managing cookies**

Most browsers also allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. You can normally change your browser settings within the ‘options’ or ‘preferences’ menu for your browser. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. You can review your Internet browser settings, typically under the sections “Help” or “Internet Options,” to exercise choices you have for certain Cookies. If you disable or delete certain cookies, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work. Please refer to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html) for information on commonly used browsers.
